I saved
over time
and paid
it off
and then
talk to
you about
scaling It's
one of
the hardest
things to
do people
will have
a great
idea They
start they
don't know
how to
scale and
grow it
Don't try
to go
to zero
to a
hundred grow
zero to
five feet
and ten
feet fifteen
Take your
time It's
a marathon
not a
sprint I
could do
this all
day If
you really
want me
to coach
don't go
for the
quick money
go for
building a
business That's
worth something
so you
thought very
long term
is what
you're saying
You didn't
think about
instant gratification
Never never
can did
you ever
lose money
have to
do it
for love
you lose
money sometimes
Yeah Yeah
I've only
closed one
office out
of 40
in my
career But
you got
to do
something that
you love
it has
to be
internal passion
You can't
get up
every day
at 4
in the
morning right
If you
don't love
it for
30 straight
years talk
to me
about customer
retention because
a lot
of people
don't get
a client
They'll lose
them within
a couple
months How
did you
maintain customers
for such
a long
time You
got to
stay the
same person
don't change
stay loyal
hungry and
become friends
You never
have customers
They become
your best
friend I
am ice
cream buy
them hot
dogs and
that's how
you get
somewhere Did
you ever
have anybody
that doubted
you in
business Oh
that's the
best people
I want
to go
after give
me that
year What's
the biggest
you said
it was
public in
terms of
revenue What's
the most
amount of
money you
made in
a year
was it
hundreds of
millions or
yeah I
gotta go
celebrate a
birthday I
get your
contact Yeah
Thank you
brother excuse
me sir
how old
were you
when you
made your
first million
I think
I was
25 How'd
you make
it that
early I
was in
mortgage banking
in San
Francisco So
did you
own a
company where
you just
did I
started a
mortgage company
It was
a mortgage
bank How'd
you get
into that
business